<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Blog</title>
    <link>https://jasonseibel.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 17:54:50 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jasonseibel.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Last While</title>
      <link>https://jasonseibel.com/posts/the-last-while/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 17:54:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasonseibel.com/posts/the-last-while/</guid>
      <description>MIT has been fun for the last while. The most surprising class has definitely been 17.811 Game Theory and Political Science. It takes both a mathematical and political approach to Game Theory and is a combined graduate and undergraduate class with about 14 students. There&amp;rsquo;s one two hour lecture a week in a cozy classroom with the professor that interjects with snippets from their research. I definitely think it is my favorite HASS (Humanities and Social Sciences) class I&amp;rsquo;ve taken at MIT so far.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Firehose and WIFI</title>
      <link>https://jasonseibel.com/posts/firehose/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2017 17:04:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasonseibel.com/posts/firehose/</guid>
      <description>Things have been busy. The gap in time between the last post and this one is perfectly indicative of how the last chunk of MIT has been. Don&amp;rsquo;t get me wrong though, everything was absolutely amazing, just super busy.
I won&amp;rsquo;t spend time talking about all of the things that happened in this post, but hopefully I&amp;rsquo;ll get around to it at some point.
HackMIT 2017 was the biggest time sink as the semester was starting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lofty Goals</title>
      <link>https://jasonseibel.com/posts/lofty-goals/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 17:45:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasonseibel.com/posts/lofty-goals/</guid>
      <description>Fell off my loft this morning. The ladder was built to only sit loose on the bed frame and slipped as I was climbing down to turn off my alarm. I fell onto the ladder and sliced the inner ball of my foot. Not even sure what my foot hit against, but my roommate and another friend got my some gauze and a wrapped it before taking a Lyft and hopping to MIT Medical, where they put these pressure bandages on it that I think they called stirrups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second Day of Classes</title>
      <link>https://jasonseibel.com/posts/second-day-of-classes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 22:25:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasonseibel.com/posts/second-day-of-classes/</guid>
      <description>I picked my classes last night and am satisfied I can use this semester as a foundation for doing a lot of interesting classes in the future. I heard from a MEng that they planned on rushing to taking a variety of grad classes so they could get exposure to lots of different fields at a higher level so they could decide what really interested them with better information than just some intro or header classes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Majors and Classes</title>
      <link>https://jasonseibel.com/posts/majors-and-classes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 00:12:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasonseibel.com/posts/majors-and-classes/</guid>
      <description>Today I think I decided to be more serious about learning more math at MIT. Understanding things from the ground up has always been my favorite way to learn and more math should make that a reality hopefully.
I took a pretest for 6.031 and passed (I think) so now I don&amp;rsquo;t have to take 6.009. 6.031 is in Java, which I have never used before. Should be fun.
Fire show was lit (lol).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I Read</title>
      <link>https://jasonseibel.com/posts/what-i-read/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 23:46:28 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jasonseibel.com/posts/what-i-read/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll start with lists of things I have read. Hopefully I&amp;rsquo;ll add ratings or commentary in the future.
https://web.williams.edu/Mathematics/lg5/Rota.pdf</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>